# from https://opentdb.com/api_config.php
question_data = [
    {"category": "Entertainment: Television",
     "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "AMC&#039;s &quot;The Walking Dead&quot;, Rick, Carl, Daryl, Morgan, Carol and Maggie were introduced to us in Season 1.",
     "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "History",
     "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The two atomic bombs dropped on Japan by the United States in August 1945 were named &#039;Little Man&#039; and &#039;Fat Boy&#039;.",
     "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge",
     "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The average woman is 5 inches \/ 13 centimeters shorter than the average man.",
     "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "History", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Theodore Roosevelt Jr. was the only General involved in the initial assault on D-Day.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Science: Computers", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "AMD created the first consumer 64-bit processor.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Vehicles",
     "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The General Motors EV1 was the first street-legal production electric vehicle.",
     "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Cartoon & Animations", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Nickelodeon rejected the pilot to Adventure Time.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Television", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Like his character in &quot;Parks and Recreation&quot;, Aziz Ansari was born in South Carolina.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "In &quot;Super Mario World&quot;, the rhino mini-boss, Reznor, is named after the lead singer of the band &quot;Nine Inch Nails&quot;.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Sound can travel through a vacuum.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The title of the 1969 film &quot;Krakatoa, East_of Java&quot; is incorrect, as Krakatoa is in fact west of Java.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Metallica collaborated with Rowan Atkinson&#039;s Mr Bean on a 1992 comic relief single.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The pickled gherkin was first added to hamburgers because a US health law required all fast-food to include a source of Vitamin C.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "During pre-production of &quot;Super Mario Bros.&quot;, Mario originally was meant to shoot bullets.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "In the game &quot;Until Dawn&quot; Emily is the only playable character who can be killed by another playable character directly.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]
